{
    "subject": "resource/Murder,_My_Sweet",
    "predicate": "property/music",
    "object": "resource/Roy_Webb",
    "human_readable": "The music in Murder, My Sweet was performed by Roy Webb.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8543095588684082,
            "question": "Who provided the soundtrack for Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8230419158935547,
            "question": "Name a musician associated with the film Murder, My Sweet."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8149980902671814,
            "question": "What was the name of the musical artist involved in Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7868509292602539,
            "question": "Who composed the music for the film Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368630528450012,
            "question": "Which film featured music by Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.596219539642334,
            "question": "What is the name of the composer who worked on Murder, My Sweet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5024482011795044,
            "question": "What musical work is Roy Webb known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22157558798789978,
            "question": "Roy Webb is famous for his work in which field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04128683730959892,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of a composer who worked on a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04099002853035927,
            "question": "Who scored the music for the movie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music in Murder, My Sweet was performed by Roy Webb.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6842_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of a composer who worked on a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6842_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roy Webb is famous for his work in which field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6842_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical work is Roy Webb known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6842_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6842_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple mentions of Roy Webb's involvement with film scores and compositions, including his work on Murder, My Sweet. For example, in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6842/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt, it is mentioned that \"music: Roy Webb\" for the 1944 film noir Murder, My Sweet. This supports the idea that Roy Webb performed the music in Murder, My Sweet."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that the music in \"Murder, My Sweet\" (1944) was performed by Roy Webb. Specifically, file_path 28.txt mentions \"Roy Webb was really a very good composer, confirmed by his illustrious career,\" and file_path 50.txt states \"music: Roy Webb.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}